nasioc.com 2016-12-21

# Privacy Policy - NASIOC

  1. NASIOC.com recognizes that you care about the personal information that is held about you and how that is used.
  2. This privacy policy applies to all personal data, submitted by you, to the NASIOC.com web site.
  3. By registering to NASIOC.com you need to submit a chosen name and contact information, more specifically an e-mail address. No extremely personal information, such as Social Security or Credit Card numbers are stored by us.
  4. NASIOC.com also stores and reads cookies to and from your computer. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our forums and general website features to recognize your browser for when you return to this web site. By using this website, you agree that both the webserver, and any trusted 3rd party we chose, such as advertising networks, may place a tracking cookie on your machine and access it at any time during your session. We allow third-party companies collect certain information when you visit our web site. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use both personally identifiable information (e.g., your name, phone number, or electronic address) and non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioural advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of Solve Media at [www.solvemedia.com](http://www.solvemedia.com/), the Digital Advertising Alliance at [http://www.aboutads.info/](https://www.aboutads.info/), the Internet Advertising Bureau at [http://www.iab.net](http://www.iab.net/), or the Network Advertising Initiative at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). In general, cookies are safe and are not a security issue when being used from 'trusted' internet sites, such as NASIOC.com. For information on how to manage cookies in your browser, please visit [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2)
  5. All other information provided by you goes into a "public profile" and is entirely optional, all information held in that profile is held there at your own risk. This info is edited via your Control Panel in the forums.
  6. You have a legal right for the personal information held at NASIOC.com to be updated if it is incorrect or deleted if you choose. Most of this can be done through your Control Panel in the forums. If you are having issues with this, please contact us if you need help.
  7. NASIOC.com will take all reasonable effort to ensure that all personal information about you submitted is maintained secure on our server. However, we make no warranty to this.
  8. This site is intended for individuals over the age of 13. Any information collected is intended to be of individuals over the age of 13. According to [COPPA](https://www.ftc.gov/coppa/index.html), our site does NOT cater to children. "Operators of commercial websites or online services directed to children under 13 that collect personal information from children" require a COPPA agreement and privacy policy. Since we do not cater to this age group, no COPPA exists on NASIOC.com
  9. This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice. It is your responsibility to check this page for updates or changes. If you have any questions regarding your privacy, then Contact Us
